Charlie Nelms papers, 1967-2016 C701
Indiana University Archives
- Audiovisual, 1979-2011
  - University of Michigan-Flint Chancellor's Inauguration, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Previous title: WFUM/28 Public Television, University of Michigan-Flint, Chancellor's Inauguration
  - 48 Hours 5/2/96, May 2, 1996; genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Previous title: WFUM/TV28, 48 Hours, May 2, 1996
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/3b591s374. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
  - Dancing on the Edge of Chaos / Documentary on Skilled work & Community Violence, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/6d570f21z. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.
    Previous title: WFUM/TV28, Dancing on the Edge of Chaos
  - University of Michigan-Flint Commencement Spring 1996, genreform: VHS (Box 11)
    Streaming access for IU users: https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/h989rm83g. Non-IU users may request streaming access by contacting the University Archives.